PEIJUN BAO

(+86)19801107587 \diamond peijunbao@pku.edu.cn \diamond Homepage

RESEARCH INTEREST

My research interest is on computer vision and machine learning problems in general. Especially, I am especially interested in problems that are practical (e.g. object detection, instance segmentation) and fundamental (e.g. self-supervised learning, transfer learning).

EDUCATION

Peking University, Beijing, China

September 2018 - Present

Master Student in Computer Science

Technical University of Madrid, Madrid, Spain

September 2016 - March 2017

Visiting Student, Sponsored by China Scholarship Council

Northwestern Polytechnical University, Xi'an, China

September 2014 - July 2018

Bachelor Student in Computer Science

GPA: 90.6/100 Ranking 1/27

Selected Courses with Grade A: Mathematical Analysis, Linear Algebra, Probability Theory, Ordinary Differential Equations, Numerical Methods, Automatic Control, Signal and System, Operating System, Algorithm Design, GPU Parallel Programming, Data Mining, etc.

PUBLICATION

Dense Events Grounding in Video

Peijun Bao, Qian Zheng and Mu Yadong

The 35th AAAI Conference on Artificial Intelligence, 2021 [pdf]

Tiny Hand Gesture Recognition without Localization via a Deep Convolutional Network,

Peijun Bao, Ana I. Maqueda, Carlos R. del-Blanco and Narciso García

IEEE Transactions on Consumer Electronics, 2018 [pdf]

RESEARCH EXPERIENCE

Machine Intelligence Lab at Peking University

September 2018 - Present

Supervisor: Prof. Mu Yadong

Image Processing Group at Technical University of Madrid September 2016 - March 2017

Supervisor: Prof. Narciso Garcia and Dr. Carlos R. del-Blanco

Medical Image Processing Lab at Northwestern Polytechnical University June 2015 -

July 2018

Supervisor: Prof. Yong Xia

HONOR & AWARDS

Merit student, Northwestern Polytechnical University Honors scholarship, Northwestern Polytechnical University Exchange Student Scholarship, China Scholarship Council